[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 4]
[الحلقة 4]
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
My leg hurts.
ساقي تؤلمني.
Come in.
ادخل.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
Let her change here.
دعها تتغير هنا.
Yes, Mr. Lu.
نعم ، السيد لو.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
شكرا لك سيد لو.
Mr. Lu left me
السيد لو تركني
such a large office.
مثل هذا المكتب الكبير.
It shows that Mr. Lu cares about me.
يظهر أن السيد لو يهتم بي.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
All the players have finished the show.
أنهى جميع اللاعبين العرض.
Calculate the total score.
احسب النتيجة الإجمالية.
Okay.
تمام.
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
As a model,
كنموذج،
you have no professional ability
ليس لديك أي قدرة مهنية
and only play tricks behind the scenes.
ولعب الحيل فقط خلف الكواليس.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
you can beat me like this?
يمكنك هزامي هكذا؟
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
You better admit it now.
من الأفضل أن تعترف بذلك الآن.
When I find it out,
عندما اكتشفت ذلك ،
you will suffer.
سوف تعاني.
- Who did this? - No idea.
- من فعل هذا؟  - لا يوجد فكرة.
Gao Jiming.
جاو جيمنج.
Bring me the high-heeled shoe in Su Manni's hand.
أحضر لي الحذاء ذو ​​الكعب العالي في يد Su Manni.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
Look at the shoe.
انظر إلى الحذاء.
Obviously someone is trying to frame me.
من الواضح أن هناك من يحاول تأذيتي.
Seek justice for me.
اطلب العدالة من أجلي.
Announce the result first.
أعلن النتيجة أولا.
The first place
المكان الأول
in the company's internal selection
في الاختيار الداخلي للشركة
is Su Manni.
هو Su Manni.
Your trick doesn't make sense.
خدعتك لا معنى لها.
The first place is still mine.
المكان الأول لا يزال لي.
Gao Jiming.
جاو جيمنج.
Go investigate monitoring.
اذهب للتحقيق في المراقبة.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
If you admit now,
إذا اعترفت الآن ،
I can consider a lighter punishment.
يمكنني التفكير في عقوبة أخف.
But if
لكن اذا
I found out who it was from the surveillance,
اكتشفت من كان من المراقبة ،
the result
النتائج
remains unknown.
ما زال مجهولا.
Mr. Lu, sorry.
السيد لو ، آسف.
Sorry.
آسف.
I didn't do it on purpose.
لم أفعل ذلك عن قصد.
Don't fire me.
لا تطردني.
Go to the finance department
اذهب إلى قسم المالية
to settle the salary.
لتسوية الراتب.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
شكرا لك سيد لو.
Manni.
رجل.
Mr. Lu supports you
السيد لو يدعمك
and upholds justice for you.
ويقيم العدل لك.
I envy you so much.
أنا أحسدك كثيرا.
When you become Huanzhen's top,
عندما تصبح قمة Huanzhen ،
don't forget us.
لا تنسونا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't forget any of you,
لن أنسى أيا منكم ،
especially you.
خصوصا أنت.
Can't you smile?
ألا تستطيع أن تبتسم؟
This will only make others feel that
هذا سيجعل الآخرين يشعرون بذلك فقط
you are being forced by me.
أنت أجبرني.
Isn't that the truth?
أليست هذه هي الحقيقة؟
We are a couple now.
نحن زوجان الآن.
We should act as a couple.
يجب أن نتصرف كزوجين.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I will cooperate with you.
سوف أتعاون معك.
So alike.
على حد سواء.
Really.
حقًا.
You look exactly like your grandma
تبدو بالضبط مثل جدتك
when she was young.
عندما كانت صغيرة.
Lu Nan, Su Bei.
لو نان ، سو باي.
You are determined
أنت مصمم
to be a couple.
ليكونا زوجين.
Nan.
في.
What's your plan?
ما هي خطتك؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
I have already arranged everything.
لقد رتبت بالفعل كل شيء.
I will announce my engagement to Su Bei
سأعلن خطبتي إلى Su Bei
at my birthday party.
في حفلة عيد ميلادي.
Okay.
تمام.
Fine.
بخير.
Now that your marriage is set,
الآن بعد أن تم تعيين زواجك ،
you should
يجب
work hard with Nan.
اعمل بجد مع نان.
When could I have
متى يمكنني
a great-grandchild?
ابن حفيد؟
Grandma!
جدتي!
Okay, no worries.
حسنا لا داعي للقلق.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
It's up to you.
الأمر متروك لك.
Nan,
في،
since you are getting engaged,
منذ خطوبتك ،
take Bei tomorrow
خذ باي غدا
to choose a ring.
لاختيار الخاتم.
So soon?
قريبا جدا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Your birthday
عيد ميلادك
and engagement
والمشاركة
are approaching.
يقتربون.
You have to take the initiative
عليك أن تأخذ زمام المبادرة
and not let Bei down.
ولا تخذل باي.
Got it, grandma.
حسنًا يا جدتي.
Seriously?
بشكل جاد؟
Don't worry, grandma.
لا تقلقي يا جدتي.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
[Lu Family's adopted daughter, Lu Feier]
[ابنة عائلة لو بالتبني ، لو فيير]
Anyone there?
أي شخص هناك؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Sorry, madam.
اسف سيدتي.
Our store was booked
تم حجز متجرنا
by Mr. Lu of Huanzhen Group today.
من قبل السيد لو من مجموعة Huanzhen اليوم.
I just came for him.
لقد جئت للتو من أجله.
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪